Deposit one lakh rupees each for 12 years. You will
accumulate 12 lakh rupees and from the 13th year itself you
can get income for the next 30 years. How many
years?
[Music]
[Praise]
Hello, how are you all? I hope you are well,
everything is well in the family.
Friends, you are very welcome
to the wonderful and amazing channel of Policy Bhandaar, where
today I have brought for you ICICI's Guaranteed Income
Plan, in which there will be Guaranteed Income
for Tomorrow, Gift Pro Plan, which
is amazing in itself and I will
share the complete details of this plan with you. Those who
want to invest in the policy, want to
understand more about this plan,
I will explain all the options to you in detail. My
only request to you is to
take an all over India basis policy, want to understand, want to
get a quotation of the plan,
give us a chance to serve you once, we will share all the details with you.
My name is Yogendra Verma, I
am in this industry for the last 28 years, I am an
insurance expert and I provide genuine
platform genuine working to the people so that
money starts flowing and
multi-grows very fast.  So friends, today I have
brought a plan under the Guaranteed Income Plan,
I have named it Guaranteed Income for
Tomorrow Gift Pro Plan. In this, I will
give only one investment option and will
give you six types of money back options. The
investment is the same. You will get six types of returns,
such amazing returns. I will
explain it to you in an amazing way. You have to
watch this video carefully, understand it and after
properly understanding it, then take this plan
through us. So let's see quickly.
Just deposit one lakh each for 12 years.
Your ₹ lakh will be deposited and from the 13th year itself,
you can take income for the next 30 years. For
how many years will you get guaranteed income for the next 30 years?
₹ lakh given
12280. You will get guaranteed income for the next 30 years. There is
no ifs and but in this and not only this, the
money you will get on maturity will be
₹
2280. Your total money that you will get is 48  You will get Rs
98400 Friends, you had given Rs ₹ one lakh and will
get Rs 48.98 lakh You had
deposited 12 lakhs one by one and will get Rs 48.98000 This is the
first option I am giving in which there is
no waiting period, there is no deferment
You gave for 12 years and started getting it from the 13th year
but if you feel that
I have to wait a little and take the money and want to
take more money then friends here there
are deferred options from 1 year to 5 years I am
quickly telling you the second option in which you have to
pay for only 12 years and wait for 1 year You
made the payment for 12 years and will wait for 1 year
You will start getting money from the 14th year
how much will you get ₹
13233 Earlier you were getting Rs 12000 Now you will get Rs
132330 It will come for full 30 years and not only this you will
get Rs 13233 on maturity You will get that as it is, you will definitely get it
Total money which will be yours will be Rs
5169900  You will pay only 12 lakhs and
get ₹69000. This is the second amazing and amazing
guaranteed version. I am telling you about it. Let's
talk about the third one. If you wait for 2 years, make
payment for 12 years and wait for 2 years, then from the
15th year onwards, you will get ₹
13840. ₹
13840 will come for the entire 30 years and the maturity amount you will get at 30 years will be ₹13840.
Total money will be ₹55 lakhs. You will get ₹15000. You will
get ₹12 lakhs. 55 lakhs is
up to you. Wait for one year, wait for zero years
or wait for two years. This is a great and amazing
working of IC Pro. Not only this, I am
also giving you the third working,
see carefully, you can get more than this. If you
pay ₹1 lakh for 12 years and wait for three years, then
how much money will you get in the 7th year? ₹
54310. On waiting for the third year, this
₹154 will come for the entire 30 years and the
same ₹13 on maturity.  54000 will be increased, you will
get ₹ 54310 The total money you will
get will be ₹
5829300 You will get 12 lakhs You will get 58 lakhs
Amazing, amazing working,
I told you the fourth option, I am giving you the fifth option, keep it in
mind, the fifth option is to
wait for 4 years You will make the payment for 12 years Wait for 4 years Paid
12 years Waited for 4 years 16 years have passed
You will get the money in the 17th year ₹ 653
530 ₹1
6553 And this money will come for full 30 years
1365 530 You will get it in the 30th year also Not only this,
your total money will become 65000
You had given 12 lakhs You will get 61 65000 This is the
fifth option I gave you and I am
giving you the last option Wait for 5 years
Make the payment for 12 years Wait for 5 years 12 and 5
17 years have passed You will get money for 18 years
How much will you get? You will get
177590, you will get it for the entire 30 years,
multiply 177590 by 30 years and
after getting it completely, you will
also get 177590 in the third year, the total amount will be 6527700. This is
amazing working
friends, whoever wants to do zero year referral,
1 year referral, 2 years,
3 years, 4 years or 5 years, if
you want to invest in any option then
you can tell us
or you want six options, you want to check, according to
1 lakh, according to 2 lakh, according to 5 lakh
or according to 10 lakh, then
we can make all that working for you and give it to you
and you can invest with us
friends this is very wonderful amazing
working if you are in younger age then you
can also go under the option of waiting for 5 years,
if you are in older age, above 40 or 45 then
zero referral  You can go into ment, you
can go into referral ment for one year,
you can make your money grow multifold in any way, you can
get guaranteed tax free returns in a very good way, those who
will invest up to ₹ lakh in this, there will be no tax on their money back
nor will there be any tax on the total money received,
this amazing and
wonderful working is available for you, those who are in
any corner of India, in any
place, can invest in this plan through us
and those who
are NRIs, are outside India and
want to invest in this plan, then
please give us a chance to serve you once, we provide
this plan on all over India, all over world basis,
Hello, your friend
Yogendra B